svbrokers.com 2019-01-23

# Privacy Policy – SVBROKERS.COM

SVBROKERS.COM always remains committed to protecting privacy of its users. Customer data security is among our primary concerns.

Below, we describe our policy in regard to protecting sensitive data we receive from our clients and using the collected information.

  1. How We Use Customer Data

To provide its services and operate its website, SVBROKERS asks its users to submit and collects some relevant information regarding their identity, visits to our and linked websites, behavioral patterns etc.

Information of another kind can be collected too, including that regarding users’ engagement in our promotional offers and events. This gives us valuable feedback to enhance our performance.

In general, the collected information is used to personalize our services and make them better and more efficient. The contact details you provide on our website can be used to contact you if any kind of communication is required. Your email address or phone number can be used to send you promotional emails, which are never spam, but thoroughly selected offers in regard to our or third-party products that we truly believe to be of interest to you. The selection is made based on the whole array of information we collect about you during your activity on our website.

Also, your data is used for accounting, payment, billing, safety, legal and administrative purposes. As a part of our activities, we collect statistics, which can help us further improve the services and products we promote and achieve better user satisfaction, which is important for us. We reserve the right to encourage you to participate in topical customer surveys. In this case, only aggregated information is collected to be used for marketing purposes. In many cases, however, we need your specific information to identify your personal preferences and requirements to be used for more personalized business relations between you and us.

If you decide to give us feedback in regard to our collaboration, you are welcome to do so. On our part, we may sometimes contact you by any channels to receive additional information, provide you an explanation or settle a problem.

We thoroughly research and analyze the collected information and use it for administrative purposes, to provide customer support, develop our website and improve user experience.

With focus on securing your privacy, we store all the collected information on our own servers or on dedicated servers provided by third party entities. In both cases, all necessary security measures are implemented. Additionally, your information sometimes may be transferred to other third-party contractors who perform on our behalf certain tasks for the purposes outlined in this Policy.

  2. Tracking

Using some kind of tracking software to identify customer browsing patterns is a common practice and a powerful tool to enhance a website’s performance. This is what we do too. This activity does not involve collecting personally identifying data, and only is to reveal general, aggregated patterns and trends.

  3. User’s Right to Check Their Personal Data

As our website’s user, you can any time request a copy of your personal data stored with us. Call records can be requested too. In the latter case, however, please, note that we delete all calls from our users after 90 days.

According to our routine procedures, we start processing your information request within ten (10) business days. To launch the process, we may require some additional information from you. If you do not provide it within a reasonable period of time, your request can be left undecided, so you will need to submit another request and start the procedure from the beginning, if you still would like to check your personal data.

All requests are to be sent to the email address given in the Contact section of our website.

  4. Data Security Protection Measures Applied

When you, as a user, communicate with the SVBROKERS.COM website over the Internet, 128-bit encryption/decryption algorithm is applied. In full compliance with applicable international data protection laws, encryption and other protective procedures are also applied to data stored on our servers. To prevent unauthorized access, we never disclose your personal data to third parties, except for cases when we are required to do so by law. Even when you request your own information from us, we will ask you to prove your identity prior to provide it to you.

As mentioned above, SVBROKERS commissions certain tasks to third party contractors, who need your information to do their job. In this case, we never provide the data unless we are sure the partner has all necessary security measures in place. The only exception is when we are required to pass the information by law.

We store your information during a reasonable period of time, unless otherwise provided for by law.

  5. Cookie Files

Cookie files contain small portions of service information. They are stored on user-end computers or mobile devices, in your browser’s system folders. They can be easily deleted as soon as the user decides to do it. Most of the times, popular browsers, are set to accept and store this kind of files automatically. At their own discretion, users can change the setting to disable cookies, in which case they still will be able to use websites. The functionality, however, will be tragically compromised.

Cookies we use contain no personally identifying data. The aggregated information stored in these files help us gauge and enhance effectiveness of our promotional and advertising endeavors. Sometimes, they can be used in emails.

With cookies, we can better understand how users perceive and navigate different pages and features of our website. As a result, we can figure out what your preferences are, for how long you stay on a particular page, which our proposals interest you the most and which ones proved to be worthless for you etc.

This kind of user-specific statistics is helpful when we generate emails to be sent to you with the most relevant offers and proposals. This information is for internal use only; we never disclose it or share with third parties. Yet, if you feel uncomfortable with this situation, you can easily disable cookies in your browser’s settings any time.

  6. Pixels

Pixels work similar to cookies, but are used with emails. They help us know whether our emails are read at all. To boost effectiveness of our emails, we can use pixels to know your email format settings – HTML or text.

  7. Data Collection Consent

By using the SVBROKERS.COM website, you give us your consent to collecting and using the above described information for the stated purposes.

If certain provisions of this Privacy Policy remain unclear to you, feel free to contact our support team. If and when any changes or amendment to this Privacy Policy occur, you can find them on this page. So you are encouraged to visit this page from time to time to be always aware of how and why we collect and use information about you.
